

Murillo Vieira e Silva

INTRODUCTION

With about 4 years of experience in the field as a Frontend (and Fullstack) developer, I've worked on important projects in all phases of the software development lifecycle, from business requirements collection to project delivery. I also have developed a business perspective mindset ever since I started to work, always focused on adding value to the company.

Yet in college, I started developing hard problem solving skills in programming marathons. I've always appreciated good challenges, specially when working with a team, where I always wanted to learn in depth to become proficient in my role as a developer.

I'm motivated about the whole software development process, management and what it includes. However, my favorite part is the coding. I'm furthermore interested in hearing from colleagues and managers to learn something new, I also enjoy sharing my experiences with them, in my opinion, that makes me more engaged.

At the present time, I'm living at Aparecida de Goiânia, Goiás - Brazil. I'm also a pianist, desiring to know different places in the world and to eat good hamburgers.

EXPERIENCE



NECTAR CRM (DEC 2018 - CURRENT)

Working on improvements for the backoffice webapp from the enterprise's main product, using ReactJs and Java Spring Framework.



ACTUAR (JUL 2017 - DEC 2018)

Development of an ERP focused on gyms and crossfit boxes management. Also maintenance a training mobile app, company websites, blogs and SEO.



META TECNOLOGIA (FEB 2017 - JUL 2017)

Improvement of a product to control financial of mobile phone stores, and payment system integration to federal government.



NUSSA SISTEMAS (JAN 2015 - JAN 2017)

Freelance website creating an maintenance and blogs for real estate companies.

EDUCATION



INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, UFG / 2015 - 2018

Bachelor degree in Information Systems Status: completed



INSTITUTE OF TECHNOLOGY, UFG / 2009 - 2014

Bachelor of Science Degree in Computer Science Status: half-way

SKILLS & ENDORSEMENTS

- Vanilla JavaScript (ES6, ES7)
- ReactJS
- React Native
- NodeJS, Express, GraphQL
- AngularJS and Angular 6.0
- Ionic 3
- SASS, LESS, STYLUS
- REST & SOAP
- Clean Code
- UI / UX, Lazy Loading and Design Pattern
- Responsive Web Design
- + Acknowledge in NoSQL databases (MongoDB) and SAAS (Firebase)

Module Bundlers: Webpack, Gulp, Grunt Versioning with Github and VSTS Agile experience with SCRUM Activities management tools: Jira, Github Issues and Trello

LICENSES & CERTIFICATIONS

React Native with NodeJS and Firebase

MERN Stack, Front to Back

Agile management with scrum

Web Design for Web Developers: UI / UX for Websites

Javascript Completo 2018 - Fundamentals to Master

SEE MORE

/murilloves

/in/murillo-vieira

murillodev.com

HOBBIES



Avoid The Asteroids | Play it free: <a> bit.ly/2lPdVJx

